The Only Website for Official Unspeakable Merchandise

Menu

Menu

Header - Shapes Theme
---------------------

* Toys
    
    * [
        
        GRAVITY TRACKS](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/gravity-tracks)
    * [
        
        SQUISH FRIENDS](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/squish-friends)
    * [
        
        QUICK PUSH FIDGET GAME](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/electronic-poplight-fidget-game)
    * [
        
        POOP CARD GAME](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/new-poop-card-games)
    * [
        
        SCENTED SLIME](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/scented-slime)
    * [
        
        MAGIC CUBE](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/magic-cube)

* Merch
    
    * [
        
        YELLOW TORNADO HUNTER T-SHIRT](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/yellow-tornado-hunter-t-shirt)
    * [
        
        BLUE TORNADO HUNTER T-SHIRT](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/blue-tornado-hunter-t-shirt)
    * [
        
        RED TORNADO HUNTER T-SHIRT](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/red-tornado-hunter-t-shirt)
    * [
        
        BLACK TORNADO HUNTER T-SHIRT](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/black-tornado-hunter-t-shirt)
    * [
        
        STREET ART T-SHIRT](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/noodle-guy-shirt)
    * [
        
        3 SILICONE WRISTBANDS](https://www.unspeakable.com/products/3-silicon-wristbands)

 Search  Close (esc)

Cart items

Privacy policy
==============

UG Merchandising LLC  
Privacy Notice

* **Overview**

This Privacy Notice describes the types of Personal Information UG Merchandising LLC (“Unspeakable,” “we,” “us,” and “our”) may collect from you when you visit https://unspeakable.com (the “Site”) or that you may provide in electronic messages between you and us. It also describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing Personal Information.

This Privacy Notice does not apply to information collected by any other website operated by Unspeakable or any third party, including our affiliates and subsidiaries, or any link that may be accessible from or through the Site.

Please read this Privacy Notice carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your Information and how we will handle it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not use the Site.

**Unspeakable may change this Privacy Notice at any time, at its discretion.** Your continued use of the Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Privacy Notice periodically for updates.

* **The Types of Information That Unspeakable Collects about You and How Unspeakable Collects Information about You**

Unspeakable may collect two types of information from you when you visit the Site: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information (collectively “Information”).

* “Personal Information” refers to data by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, and telephone number.
* “Non-Personal Information” means data that is about you but does not identify you specifically. If you do nothing during your visit to our Site but browse, read pages, or view content, we will gather and store Information about your visit that does not identify you personally.

We collect Information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* From other sources or third parties.
* Automatically as you navigate through the Site.
* Through third-party analytics.

Information You Provide Directly to Unspeakable. The Information that you provide us directly through our Site may include:

* Information that you provide to Unspeakable by registering with or filling in forms on our Site, including our “Contact Us” form. We may also ask you for Information when you report a problem with our Site. It may also be necessary for you to provide us with Information so we can communicate with you about an inquiry you have made.
* Information that you provide when you complete a transaction through our Site, such as your name, billing address, shipping address, etc.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses) if you contact us.
* Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete.
* Information you provide through use of your account on the Site,

Information Unspeakable Automatically Collects from You. The Information that Unspeakable may automatically collect and store about you when you visit the Site may include:

* The Internet Protocol Address and domain name used. The Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer. We use the Internet Protocol Address to direct internet traffic to you.
* The type of browser and operating system you used when accessing the Site.
* The date and time you visited the Site.
* The webpages or services you accessed at the Site.
* The length of time you spent on a particular page on the Site.
* The search terms you enter.
* The website you visited prior to coming to the Site.
* The actions you take on the Site, through our use of Facebook Pixels.

Google Analytics Advertising Features. We also may have the following Google Analytics advertising features implemented: Demographics and Interest reporting, Remarketing, GDN Impression Reporting, and Double Click Campaign Manager. These features collect data using Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. Unspeakable and third-party vendors use these first-party cookies to access the success of online marketing campaigns, inform future campaigns and improve the usability of the Site. To learn how to opt out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use, please see Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs for the web at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Web Beacons. Web Beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that are used to track the online movements of web or mobile application users. Unlike cookies, which are stored on a computer’s hard drive or your smartphone, web beacons are small graphics that are embedded invisibly on, for example, web pages or in HTML-based emails. Our third-party analytics providers may place web beacons on the Site that track what other websites you visit (both before and after visiting the Site). Our third-party analytics providers use information obtained from web beacons to help us improve our business and services. We do not control the use of web beacons by third parties.

Cookies. Cookies are small text files that a web server (such as Unspeakable‘s or its chosen web hosting company server) places on a user's computer. When accessing a cookie, Unspeakable’s server reads a number associated with a browser but is unable to determine any data about a user. With that number, our web server can tailor its content to the needs of the specific browser, and we can optimize the Site for your use. Unspeakable may use the following types of cookies:

* Strictly Necessary Cookies: Strictly necessary cookies are classified as cookies that must be present for the Site to provide the basic functions of the website. These cookies are essential for you to browse the Site and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Site. Cookies that allow Unspeakable to hold your items in your cart while you are shopping on our website is an example of strictly necessary cookies. **Site users cannot opt out of necessary cookies.**
* \_session\_id: allows our ecommerce platform to store information about your session.
* \_shopify\_visit: used by the Site provider’s internal statistic tracker to record the number of visits.
* \_shopify\_uniq: counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer. No data is held after midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day.
* storefront\_digest: used to determine if the current visitor has access to areas of the Site that require a password.

We ask you for your consent to use analytics cookies when you visit the Site. You can make changes by visiting our consent management platform here. If you have questions or concerns regarding how we use cookies on the Site, you can contact us [here](https://www.unspeakable.com/pages/contact-us).

* **How Unspeakable Uses Personal Information It Collects about You and the Purpose for the Collection and Use**

We use Information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information, for the following purposes:

* To present our Site and the Site Contents (as defined in the Terms of Use) to you.
* To operate, manage, and administer your transactions through the Site and account.
* To provide you with data or services that you request from us. For example, when you provide your name and email address to contact us, we are able to use your email address to respond to your comments or questions personally.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To personalize our services and advertising to you.
* To create new products or services or to improve our business and the products and services we provide you.
* To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
* To communicate with you regarding our products and services, including for marketing purposes.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the Information.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

Site statistics are compiled into traffic reports, which help Unspeakable understand, anticipate, and respond to user needs. If we learn, for example, of heightened interest in certain aspects of Unspeakable’s projects, we are likely to highlight that information on the Site home page. This helps us create a better overall experience for Site users.

Unspeakable will retain your Personal Information as long as Unspeakable believes it is needed for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice, including to provide the products and services you have requested, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and achieve other purposes described under this Privacy Notice. The exact amount of time will vary based on the nature of the Personal Information but will not exceed legal limits.  

* **How Unspeakable Protects Your Personal Information**

We have implemented measures designed to protect your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. Unfortunately, the internet is not completely secure. Although we are working to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Information either in transmission or when stored. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

Shopify provides us with an ecommerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. You can find more information about Shopify’s policies on Shopify’s [website](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).  

* **When Unspeakable Shares Your Personal Information**

We may use and disclose Non-Personal Information about our users without restriction. We may disclose Personal Information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Notice:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates, including third-party payment facilitators such as Shopify.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business, as described further below.
* To a buyer or other successor (potential or actual) in connection with a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Unspeakable’s assets, including any related due diligence.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide Personal Information.
* With your consent.
* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply our Terms of Use.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Unspeakable or others.

Except as described above, Unspeakable does not share or sell any of your Information.  

* **Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf**

We use third parties to host the Site, design and operate the Site features, and perform administrative, payment processing, analytics, and communication. Services these third parties provide include enabling Unspeakable to send you emails regarding the items in your shopping cart and providing Information to Unspeakable about the use of the Site and viewing of our content. These third parties also permit you to complete purchases of our products. We may disclose your Information to these companies so they can carry out these services.  

* **Information From Children Under 16**

**Unspeakable complies with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and related regulations. The Site is not directed at children, and Unspeakable does not knowingly collect, use, or disclose Information from children under 16. If Unspeakable learns that a child under 16—or the equivalent minimum age depending on the jurisdiction, such as 13 in the United States per the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act—has provided Personal Information, Unspeakable will delete this Personal Information from our databases. If you are under 16, do not use this Site or provide any Personal Information about yourself to Unspeakable, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. If you become aware that Personal Information of a child under 16 years of age has been provided, please contact us at** **unspeakablemerch@gmail.com****.  
  
**

* **Links to Other Websites and Services**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Site, including the information or content contained therein. Our Privacy Notice does not apply to third-party websites or services.  

* **Do Not Track**

Some browsers incorporate a "Do Not Track" (“DNT”) feature that, when turned on, signals to websites and online services that you do not want to be tracked. At this time, the Site does not respond to DNT signals.  

* **Your Choices about Personal Information**

If you choose not to provide us with certain Personal Information, you may be unable to access or use some portions of the Site. We send promotional and marketing communications only with your consent. If you no longer wish to receive these or other communications, click on the “unsubscribe link” provided in such communications.

Please report your concerns about collection or use of Personal Information through the Site [here](https://www.unspeakable.com/pages/contact-us) or by sending an email to unspeakablemerch@gmail.com.  

* **Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and the United Kingdom (“UK”)**

If you are located in the EEA or UK, you may have certain rights under local law with respect to your personal data that are described below. The Site is not intended for users located in the EEA or UK who are under the age of 16. If you are located in the EEA or UK and are under the age of 16, do not use the Site.

Controller of Personal Information. Unspeakable is the Controller of your Personal Information. Unspeakable’s primary place of business is 15080 Sommermeyer Ste 100, Houston, Texas 77041.

Processing. Unspeakable may process your Personal Information on one or more of the following legal bases:

* As necessary to enter into a contract with you or a legal entity you represent, to perform our contractual obligations, to provide services, to respond to requests from you, or to provide customer support;
* Where we have a legitimate interest, as described in this Privacy Notice (see “How Unspeakable Uses Personal Information It Collects about You and the Purpose for Collection and Use”);
* As necessary to comply with relevant law and legal obligations, including to respond to lawful requests and orders; or
* With your consent.

Your Rights. Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to:

* Ask whether we hold Personal Information about you and request copies of such Personal Information and information about how it is processed;
* Request that inaccurate Personal Information is corrected;
* Request deletion of Personal Information that is no longer necessary for the purposes underlying the processing, processed based on withdrawn consent, or processed in non-compliance with applicable legal requirements;
* Request us to restrict the processing of Personal Information where the processing is inappropriate;
* Object to the processing of Personal Information;
* Request portability of Personal Information that you have provided to us (which does not include information derived from the collected information), where the processing of such Personal Information is based on consent or a contract with you and is carried out by automated means; and
* Lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authorities.

You can exercise your rights above by contacting us [here](https://www.unspeakable.com/pages/contact-us) or at **unspeakablemerch@gmail.com**.

When your consent is the basis for our processing of your Personal Information, you may withdraw your consent at any time, and we will stop any further processing of your data for that purpose.

The categories of Personal Information that Unspeakable collects are identified in “The Types of Information Unspeakable Collects about You and How Unspeakable Collects Personal Information about You.” Additional information about how long Unspeakable will retain your Personal Information and how it shares your Personal Information is found in the section “How Unspeakable Uses Personal Information It Collects about You and the Purpose for the Collection and Use,” and the section “When Unspeakable Shares Your Personal Information,” found above. Currently, we have disabled all non-necessary cookies and passive collection of Personal Information from our website for EEA and UK users.

* **How To Contact Us about this Privacy Notice**

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Notice and our privacy practices, please contact us at unspeakablemerch@gmail.com or by mail at:

ATTN: Unspeakable  
UG Merchandising LLC  
2211 Rayford Rd, Ste 111  
PO Box 444  
Spring, TX 77386

EFFECTIVE DATE: July 10, 2023

Shopping sections of the Unspeakable website are intended only for users that are 16 years of age or older.

© 2024, [Unspeakable](https://www.unspeakable.com/). [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
